cloudberrylab.com 2019-07-09

# Privacy Policy | CloudBerry Lab

## CloudBerry Lab Privacy policy

Effective date: May 25, 2018

This CloudBerry Lab Privacy Policy (the "Privacy Policy") describes how CloudBerry Lab and its affiliates (together, "CloudBerry Lab" or "we") gather and process your information. CloudBerry Lab Ltd. recognizes the importance of protecting your personal information and is committed to safeguarding your privacy online.

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. When you submit information to us, you consent to the processing of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH ANY PART OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, THEN PLEASE DO NOT USE THE SERVICES.

### Where This Privacy Policy Applies

This Privacy Policy applies to use of public portions of CloudBerryLab.com (including <https://www.cloudberrycentral.com/>), registered users of our [standalone products](https://www.cloudberrylab.com/products.aspx), and registered users of the CloudBerry Managed Backup Service ([https://mbs.cloudberrylab.com](https://mbs.cloudberrylab.com/), [https://mspbackups.com](https://mspbackups.com/)) (collectively, the **"Services"** ). If a particular part of the Services posts its own privacy policy (for example, such as the Privacy Policy for the CloudBerry Managed Backup Service), then that policy, not this Privacy Policy, applies when inconsistent.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to information that is collected by any third-party website or service that you access through the Services.

The EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) is a regulation in EU law on data protection and privacy for all residents within the European Union. It requires businesses to protect the personal data and privacy of EU citizens. It also requires that companies have appropriate data security in place to protect personal data. The GDPR comes into force on May 25, 2018.

CloudBerry Lab is compliant with new regulation requirements. It acts as a data processor for customers personal data; all processing of personal data is performed in accordance with privacy rights and regulations following the GDPR. Check out our GDPR statement.

### Modifications to This Privacy Policy

We may revise and update this Privacy Policy and will post the most current version on our website. If these changes meaningfully reduce your rights, we will notify you in advance. The Effective Date of this Privacy Policy is specified at the top of this webpage.

### Information We Collect

Website: We use cookies to provide better service to you when you use our website. By using cookies, CloudBerry Lab may collect your navigation history and monitor how you use our websites and services. We use your IP address to help identify you and your location.

Marketing: When you subscribe for our newsletter or information letter about the Services updates, you are asked for your name and email address.

Services Registration: When you register for our Services you provide us your personal information: First name, Last name, Email, Phone, Company name, and other details related to your business size and purpose of usage.

Device information: We collect information from and about the devices you use to access the Services. This includes things like IP addresses to identify your location, the operating system you use, and identifiers (HID) associated with your devices.

Customer Service: When you request technical support, we collect the information you give us by sending diagnostic logs (name, email, diagnostic information and configuration).

### How We Process Personal Information

CloudBerry Lab may share non-personal, summary information regarding its customers with partners or other third parties. However, any individual customer's information provided for partners or third parties under contract with CloudBerry Lab shall be used only to perform or complete a necessary transaction or function related to the customer's purchase. These transactions or functions shall be in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy. CloudBerry Lab will not share any individual customer's information with anyone except the contracted partners and third parties mentioned above, without first receiving the individual's prior written approval. In some cases, CloudBerry Lab may use a visitor's personal information to understand overall patterns for website, Services usage, to contact the user for clarification on inaccurate information, or to follow up on a customer service issue. Personal information may include name, email, phone number, etc.

CloudBerry Lab processes personal data to set up, maintain and control your account, to communicate with you by providing feedback/report issue forms and chat. We also process your personal information to provide and improve our Services, as well as for the following purposes: usage analytics, managing support and contact requests.

We may disclose your personal information to trusted third parties who act for or on our behalf for further processing (such as storage or payment systems) and if we determine that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to comply with the law. In all other cases we do not share or distribute your personal data.

### Protection & Retention of Personal Information

We provide the security of your personal information by using an SSL certificate on transfers and we store the provided information on secure servers. If a password is used to protect your accounts and personal information, it is your responsibility for the confidentiality and security of your password and you agree to change your password regularly. Do not share your password with anyone you don't intend to.

Personal data is stored as long as you use our Services. Once you decide to stop using the Services, we can completely remove the account from our database. Also you can ask to restrict processing in accordance with data protection laws, as well as to object to any direct marketing from us, and to be informed about any automated notifications that we use. You can elect not to receive marketing communications by following the unsubscribe instruction in such communications.

### Links to Other Sites

The Services may include links to third-party websites and services that are not operated by us. When you click these links, you will be directed away from the Services. A link to a third-party website or service does not mean that we endorse it or the quality or accuracy of information presented on it. If you decide to visit a third-party website or service, you are subject to its privacy practices and policies, not ours. We encourage you to be aware of this when you leave our site, and to read the Privacy Policy of each and every website that you visit. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any personal data that you provide to these other websites and services.

### Cookies

A cookie is a small piece of information that a website stores on your computer. When you revisit the website, your browser sends the information back to that site. A cookie does not contain any Personal Information. The use of cookies is not required to browse through our site but it does enable us to better serve you when you return to our site by recording how and when you use it. You can set your browser to refuse cookies, but if you do, you might not be able to take full advantage of our site.

### Children’s Privacy

The Services are not directed to or intended for use by minors. Consistent with the requirements of the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, if we learn that we have received any information directly from a child under age 13 without a parent’s verified consent, we will use that information only to respond directly to that child (or their parent or legal guardian) to inform the child that they cannot use the Services.

If you have any questions, please contact us at [contact@cloudberrylab.com](mailto:contact@cloudberrylab.com).
